A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Policy Office, Records, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- III. Legislative Files, 2006-2009 (accession 44701)., Extent: 33.60 cubic feet (96 boxes). (Box 49-141, 170-172)
  - 2006 Regular Session
    - House of Delegates
      - HB 1539 (06) Retail Sales and Use Tax; Exemption for Gas and Oil, Extends Sunset Provision, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - HB 1540 (06) Waterworks; Tampering with Considered Crime, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - HB 1541 (06) Electric Utility Restructuring; Net Energy Metering, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - HB 1543 (06) Rural Addition Program; Funds Allocated to Any County, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 20)
      - HB 1545 (06) Tobacco Settlement Foundation; Appointment of Director, vetoed 10 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - HB 1546 (06) Reckless Driving; Change Definition thereof, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - HB 1547 (06) Alma C. White Memorial Bridge, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - HB 1554 (06) Residential Property Disclosure Act; Seller of Historic Property to Provide Notice to Purchaser, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - HB 1562 (06) Residential Property Disclosure Act; Disclosure of Previous Mining and Presence of Abandoned Mines, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 25)
      - HB 1571 (06) Referendum Elections; Provide for Preparation and Printing of Explanation for Each Question thereof, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 26)
      - HB 1575 (06) Utility Easements; Considered to Touch and Concern Servient Estate, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 27)
      - HB 1577 (06) Concealed Handgun Permits; Renewal thereof, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 28)
      - HB 1579 (06) Volunteer Firefighters' and Rescue Squad Workers' Service Award Fund Board; Membership Changes, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 29)
      - HB 1581 (06) Interstate Route 81 Corridor; Diversion of Truck Traffic, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 30)
      - HB 1582 (06) Local Government and School Divisions; Cooperative Transportation Agreements Between, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 31)
      - HB 1583 (06) Identity Theft; Protection of Incapacitated People thereof, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 32)
      - HB 1584 (06) Manufactured Housing Lot Rental Act; Owners to Charge Residents for Actual Utility Costs and Services, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 33)
      - HB 1588 (06) Declaration of Policy; Requirement for Home Instruction of Children, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 34)
      - HB 1589 (06) Family Day Homes; Unlawful to Operate Family Day Home if Any Employee is Convicted Sex Offender, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 35)
      - HB 1597 (06) Blue Star Memorial Highway, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 62, Folder 36)
      - HB 1602 (06) Day of Recognition for Early Childhood and Day-care Providers, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 62, Folder 37)
      - HB 5002 (Budget Bill), signed 30 June 2006 (Box 62, Folder 38)
      - HB 5012 (06) Budget Bill; Additional Appropriations for 2004-2006 Biennium, signed 9 June 2006 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - HB 5019 Estate Tax and Land Preservation Tax Credit; Changes in Provisions therefor, Report, amended 26 August 2006 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - 2006 Special Session
    - House of Delegates
      - HB 5032 (06) Budget Bill; Additional Appropriations for 2007-2008 Biennium, signed 25 October 2006 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - HB 5061 (06) Height of Vehicles; Increases Penalties, signed 10 October 2006 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - HB 5063 (06) VDOT; Commissioner to Annually Report on Actions and Initiatives that Involve Outsourcing, etc., signed 10 October 2006 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - HB 5064 (06) Transportation Board; Responsible for Promoting Private Investment in Transportation Infrastructure, signed 10 October 2006 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - HB 5071 (06) Maintenance and Asset Management; Clarifies Definition thereof, signed 10 October 2006 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Legislative Action Summaries (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - 2006 Regular Session
    - Senate
      - SB 6 (06) Court-appointed Counsel; Court May Appoint Those Not on Indigent Defense Commission List, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - SB 8 (06) Motor Vehicle Registration, Licensing and Certificates of Title; Offenses Relating thereto, Penalty, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - SB 12 (06) Trout Fishing; Department of Game and Inland Fisheries to Issue Special Permits for Handicapped, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - SB 13 (06) Access Road; Allocation of Funds for those Leading to Industrial Sites, etc., signed 31 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - SB 19 (06) Administrative Law Advisory Committee; Technical Amendments to Appointment Provisions, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - SB 21 (06) Internet; Simplifies and Updates References thereto in Code, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - SB 22 (06) Child Abuse or Neglect; Change in Requirement for 'Safe Haven' Law Pertaining to Infants, amended 18 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - SB 23 (06) Charter; City of Emporia, signed 13 February 2006 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - SB 25 (06) Social Services; City Council Member Appointed to Local Board, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - SB 26 (06) Assault and Battery; Limited Exception to Charges for Certain School Personnel, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - SB 28 (06) Higher Educational Institutions Bond Act of 2006; Created, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - SB 34 (06) Standards of Learning Assessments; Release thereof, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - SB 38 (06) Agritourism Activity Liability; Created, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - SB 39 (06) Test Security Procedures; Board of Education to Review Violations of Regulations by Local School Board, signed 1 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - SB 40 (06) Higher Education; New College Institute Created, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - SB 42 (06) Income Tax, State; Dept. of Taxation to Obtain Information on Taxpayers Claiming Earned Income Tax Credit, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - SB 46 (06) Local Housing Rehabilitation Zones; Created, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - SB 48 (06) Kinship Foster Care; Social Services to Seek thereof, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - SB 51 (06) Local Government; Voluntary Settlements that Provide for Annexation Take Effect by Certain Date, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 27)
      - SB 52 (06) Occoneechee State Park; Lease Extended, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 28)
      - SB 53 (06) Speed Limits; Increases Maximum Speed on Interstate Route 85, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 29)
      - SB 54 (06) Southern Virginia Higher Education Center; Modifies Membership of Board of Trustees, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 30)
      - SB 57 (06) Solid Waste Management Plans; Units to Maintain Recycling and Target Rates, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 31)
      - SB 62 (06) Comparative Religion; Board of Education to Authorize Elective Course in Grades 9 through 12, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 32)
      - SB 66 (06) School Calendars; Reduction of State Aid When Length of School Term Below What is Required, signed 1 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 33)
      - SB 67 (06) Standards of Learning Assessments; Testing Annually in Grades Three through Eight, Report, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 34)
      - SB 69 (06) Taxation; Conformity thereof with Internal Revenue Code, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 35)
      - SB 70 (06) Income Taxes, State; Payments to Producers of Quota Tobacco and Tobacco Quota Holders, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 36)
      - SB 71 (06) Standards of Quality; Biennial Review; Change to Even-numbered Years and Technical Amendment, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 37)
      - SB 72 (06) Contractors, Board of; Educational Requirements as Condition for Licensure, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 38)
      - SB 73 (06) Retail Sales and Use Tax; Exemption Includes Certain Medicines and Drugs, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 39)
      - SB 74 (06) Teacher Licensure Requirements; Revising Current Statutes and Teacher Education Program Provisions, signed 1 March 2006 (Box 63, Folder 40)
      - SB 75 (06) School Crisis, Emergency Management and Medical Emergency Response Plan; Required, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - SB 76 (06) Freedom of Information Act; Disclosure of Procurement Records Under PPTA and PPEA, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - SB 77 (06) Post-Disaster Anti-Price Gouging Act; Time of Disaster, Declared State of Emergency, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - SB 78 (06) Stock Corporation Act; Mergers to Form Holding Companies, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - SB 79 (06) Unemployment Compensation, Commission on; Repeals Sunset Provision, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - SB 81 (06) Charter; City of Richmond, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - SB 82 (06) Solid Waste Containers; Requirements for Containers Carrying Nonhazardous Waste on State Waters, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - SB 83 (06) Trapping; Exempts Trappers Using Body Grip Traps that are Completely Submerged, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - SB 85 (06) Retail Sales and Use Tax; Gratuities or Service Charges on Meals Excluded when Calculating, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - SB 86 (06) Transient Occupancy Tax; Imposition for Occupancy of any Room or Space, etc., signed 24 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - SB 87 (06) Outdoor Advertising; Vegetation Control, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - SB 88 (06) Mercury Switches in Motor Vehicles; Requires Removal Prior to their Demolition, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - SB 89 (06) Recording Devices in Motor Vehicles; Notification Required by Manufacturer, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - SB 90 (06) Electronic Recording Devices in Motor Vehicles; Ownership of Recorded Data, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - SB 95 (06) Cluster Development; Exempts Property Located in an Air Installation Compatible Use Zone, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - SB 97 (06) SOL Assessments; Fire Drills, etc., Prohibited in Schools During Periods of Mandatory Testing, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - SB 98 (06) Risk Management Plan; to include Meals on Wheels Association, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - SB 99 (06) Retirement System; Qualifications of Retired Persons Teaching in Critical Shortage Positions, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - SB 100 (06) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Alcohol Vaporizing Devices Prohibited, Penalty, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - SB 106 (06) Waste Discharge Permits; Consent of Local Governing Body Required Before Water Control Board Issues, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - SB 107 (06) Martin Luther King, Jr. Living History and Public Policy Center; Amending Governing Structure thereof, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - SB 108 (06) Employee Stock Ownership Plan; Authorizes Option Plans, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - SB 109 (06) Governor's Development Opportunity Fund; Changes thereto, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - SB 110 (06) Retail Sales Tax and Use Tax; Exemptions Include Medicines and Drugs Purchased by Nursing Homes, etc., signed 24 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - SB 112 (06) Tuberculosis; Establishing Library of Isolates for Purpose of Disease Strain Analysis, signed 7 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - SB 113 (06) Banks; Allows for Deduction of Customary Fees Without First Having to Submit an Invoice, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - SB 114 (06) Courts; Certain Matters to be Entered on Civil Order Book, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - SB 115 (06) Retirement System; Benefit Restoration Plans, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - SB 116 (06) Immunizations; Minimum Requirements for Children Entering Public or Private Schools or Centers, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 29)
      - SB 117 (06) Immunizations; Adds Booster Does of Tdap in Accordance with Board's Regulation for Certain Children, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 30)
      - SB 118 (06) Landlord and Tenant; Not to be Evicted for Certain Disturbances that Occur on Leased Premises, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 31)
      - SB 119 (06) Donor Registry; Created, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 32)
      - SB 120 (06) Protective Orders; Respondent to Pay Deposits to Connect or Restore Utility Services, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 33)
      - SB 121 (06) Tuition, In-State; Eligibility for Certain Military Personnel and Dependents, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 34)
      - SB 129 (06) Juveniles; If Gang Affiliated Certain Information to be Released by an Law-Enforcement Officer, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 35)
      - SB 134 (06) Towing and Recovery Operators; Regulation by Board for Towing and Recovery Operators, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 64, Folder 36)
      - SB 139 (06) Military Family Relief Fund; Created, Report, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 64, Folder 37)
      - SB 141 (06) Campaign Finance Disclosure Act of 2006; Reorganizes and Clarifies Provisions in the Act, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - SB 146 (06) Methamphetamine Precursor Drugs; Sale of Ephedrine and Pseudoephedrine with Restrictions, Penalty, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - SB 147 (06) Charter; Clifton Forge, signed 14 February 2006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - SB 152 (06) Motor Vehicle Dealers; Warranty Obligations, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - SB 156 (06) Appeals, Court of; Additional Compensation for Chief Judge, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - SB 157 (06) Courts Technology Fund; Created, Increase in Certain Fees, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - SB 162 (06) Administrative Process Act; Exempts Regulations Adopted by Board for Housing and Community Development, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - SB 164 (06) Waste and Water Authorities; Powers Regarding Cost Reserves and Expenditures for Operating Capital, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - SB 165 (06) Judiciary Members; Not Required to Disclose Personal Information on Statement of Economic Interests, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - SB 167 (06) Child Support; Clarifies Factors that Court May Consider in Deviating from Guideline Amount, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - SB 168 (06) Child Support; Employer Shall Prorate Amount if there is more than One Withholding Order, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - SB 169 (06) Support Orders; Changes the Effective Date thereof, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - SB 173 (06) Port Authority; Allows Police thereof to Provide Security for Private Terminal Operators, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - SB 182 (06) Community Integration Advisory Commission; Created, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - SB 183 (06) Machete; Illegal to Brandish Machete in Manner to Induce Fear, Penalty, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - SB 184 (06) Housing Programs; Creating and Implementing for Ex-Offenders, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - SB 186 (06) Roll-Back Taxes; Local Use Value Assessment Ordinances, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - SB 187 (06) Prescription Monitoring Program; Modifies Reporting Requirements, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - SB 188 (06) Health and Human Resources, Secretary of; Duties, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - SB 190 (06) Group Homes and Residential Facilities; Suspension of Licenses under Certain Circumstances, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - SB 191 (06) All-Terrain Vehicles and Off-Road Motorcycles; Owners Must Obtain Title from DMV, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - SB 193 (06) Highway Construction Funds; Allocation for Rail Projects, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - SB 194 (06) License Plates, Temporary; Issuance to Dealers by DMV, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - SB 196 (06) Highways; Allows Local Employees to Build that are Funded by State, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - SB 198 (06) Rail Advisory Board; Members Not Subject to Certain Provisions, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 25)
      - SB 199 (06) Automobile Graveyards and Junkyards; Adds City of Newport News to Localities that may Require Screening, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 26)
      - SB 200 (06) Dogs; Regulation of those that may be Dangerous, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 27)
      - SB 201 (06) Contractor Transaction Recovery Act; Streamlines Administrative Processing of Claims, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 28)
      - SB 202 (06) Charter; City of Charlottesville, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 29)
      - SB 203 (06) Public School Authority; Implement a Pass-Through of Refunding to Savings to a Locality, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 30)
      - SB 213 (06) O. Winston Link Trail; VDOT to Place and Maintain Markers Directing Travelers, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 31)
      - SB 214 (06) Health Professions; Reinstatement Hearing for Mandatory Suspension or Revocation of License, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 65, Folder 32)
      - SB 217 (06) Conservators, Guardians and Administrators; Nonprofit Organization can be Named that of an Estate, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 33)
      - SB 224 (06) Environmental Site Assessments; Localities to Adopt Ordinance Requiring, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 34)
      - SB 227 (06) Campaign Finance Disclosure; Changes Amount of Credit Card Reimbursement from Petty Cash, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 35)
      - SB 228 (06) Campaign Finance Disclosure; Filing and Reporting not to Include Tax Exempt Organizations, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 65, Folder 36)
      - SB 230 (06) Campaign Finance Disclosure; Increases Amount that Triggers Reporting Requirements, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - SB 244 (06) Statewide Independent Living Fund; Created, Report, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - SB 250 (06) Conditional Release; Extends Custody Period Following Revocation thereof Before Treatment, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - SB 251 (06) Expert Witness; Eliminates Prohibition Against Compensation in Certain Criminal Cases, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - SB 252 (06) Health Partnership Authorities, Local; Repeals Sunset Provision, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - SB 253 (06) Child Abuse and Neglect; Reporting Requirements by Ministers of Religion, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - SB 255 (06) Confidentially of Documents; Establish Protections for Materials Obtained by SCC, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - SB 257 (06) Child Day Program; Exemption from Licensure for Programs of Recreational Activities, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - SB 259 (06) Higher Educational Institutions; to Report Assignment of any Intellectual Property Interests, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - SB 260 (06) Retail Sales and Use Tax; Expands Exemption for Machinery, Tools and Industrial Materials, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - SB 261 (06) Manufacturing Development Commission; Created, Report, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - SB 262 (06) Virginia Energy Plan; Created, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - SB 265 (06) Political Campaign Advertisements; Increases Civil Penalty, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - SB 269 (06) Condominium Act; Conversion Condominiums and Notice to Locality, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - SB 271 (06) Public Procurement Act; Purchase of Certain Insurance in Construction Projects, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - SB 273 (06) Affordable Dwelling Unit Ordinance; Arlington County Permitting Certain Densities in Comprehensive Plan, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - SB 274 (06) Stormwater Management; Certain Localities Required to Adopt Program Related thereto, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - SB 280 (06) Charter; City of Norfolk, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - SB 281 (06) Dentists and Dental Hygienists; Not Required to Display Licenses when Volunteering for Charitable Organization, signed 7 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - SB 282 (06) Golf Carts; Operation thereof on Public Highways Nonapplicable in Town of Saxis, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - SB 283 (06) Arts and Cultural Districts; Includes Town of Chincoteague, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - SB 287 (06) Income Tax, State; Credit for Purchase of Long-Term Care Insurance, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - SB 288 (06) Insanity; Hearing on Revocation of Conditional Release to be Expedited, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - SB 289 (06) Insanity; Conditional Release shall not be Revoked Because of Voluntary Hospital Admission, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - SB 291 (06) Extorting Money; Person Accused thereof will be Guilty of Class 5 Felony, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 25)
      - SB 298 (06) District Courts; Remove Case to Circuit Court if Dismissal on Basis that Statute is Unconstitutional, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - SB 299 (06) DUI of Alcohol or Drugs; Maximum Punishment, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 27)
      - SB 300 (06) Spousal Support; Expedited Hearing for Member Armed Forces Reserves or National Guard, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 28)
      - SB 302 (06) Taxes, Local; Use of Collection Agents, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 29)
      - SB 303 (06) Motor Vehicle Renting Companies; Charge of Vehicle Licensing Fee, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 30)
      - SB 304 (06) Commonwealth Transportation Board, vetoed 4 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 31)
      - SB 305 (06) School Buses; Vehicle Classification and Endorsements, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 32)
      - SB 306 (06) Motor Vehicle Dealers; Increases Bond Requirements, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 33)
      - SB 312 (06) Emissions Inspection Program; Exemption of Certain Vehicles, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 34)
      - SB 313 (06) Voter Registration; DMV to Furnish List of Non-Citizens to Board of Elections, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 35)
      - SB 318 (06) Sexually Violent Predators; Monitoring and Supervision of those on Conditional Probation, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 36)
      - SB 324 (06) Teachers; Salary should be Competitive Rate Relative to Member States in Southern Regional Education Board, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 37)
      - SB 327 (06) Alcoholic Beverage; Mixed Beverage Restaurant Licenses, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 38)
      - SB 330 (06) Legislative Appointees on Certain Boards, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 66, Folder 39)
      - SB 342 (06) School Board; Referendum in Page County on Question of whether should be Elected Biennially, signed 1 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 40)
      - SB 344 (06) Gangs; Person on Probation Prohibited from any Contact, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 41)
      - SB 345 (06) False Identification Cards; Used for Establishing Residency, Penalty, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 66, Folder 42)